<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Silicon Valley's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Brett Jennings, a top Real Estate Agent in Silicon Valley, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 13:38:11 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 13:38:11 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bring Calm to Clients in Times of Crisis</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jvBPQpB5IBI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m sharing some tips for how you can reassure your clients in these difficult times. Any client right now has some uncertainty or fear about the coronavirus, the market, and where things may be heading. During a crisis or crash, real estate is still the safest place to be. It’s not as if we haven’t seen crises and crashes before. In 2008 we had both the financial collapse and the colossal recession that followed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any more questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me! I’d love to be of value to you, so just let me know what I can do to help.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 16:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/bring-calm-to-clients-in-times-of-crisis.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/bring-calm-to-clients-in-times-of-crisis.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Leverage Listings &amp; Leads to Get 5 Contracts in 1 Week</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/B47YnT93O_I?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don Mitchell and I have known each other for quite some time—he’s been in the real estate business for over 20 years, and I met him when I was first getting started 12 years ago. I wanted to share his success story with you. We’ve decided to partner up, and since Don joined the Real Estate Experts Group, his business has been exploding! &lt;strong&gt;In the last week alone he’s gotten five contracts, which is between five and six million dollars in sales.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate is a roller coaster, and I wanted to make sure great, solo agents could benefit from being a part of our group. Don isn’t directly part of my team, but he’s able to take advantage of all the leverage, leads, systems, and support we offer. Don’s goal is to help 40 families move this year, and he’s already well on his way to that objective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Since Don joined the Real Estate Experts, his business has been exploding!%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-leverage-listings-leads-to-get-5-contracts-in-1-week.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Since Don joined the Real Estate Experts, his business has been exploding!”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don says it doesn’t matter how long you’ve been in the business, as long as you’re coachable. If you can understand and then implement the systems you’re taught, it works wonderfully. “Don’t worry about being perfect,” he says. “Right now is about making things happen.” I know Don is going to reach his goals this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re considering growing your business, that’s what we want to help you do.&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re currently doing between five and 20 deals per year and you want to make between 15 and 50 deals per year, that’s achievable. We can help you do it because we have put a ton of time into developing these systems and making sure they work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about our business or how you can get involved, please reach out to us via phone or email. We would love to speak with you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 17:04:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-leverage-listings-leads-to-get-5-contracts-in-1-week.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-leverage-listings-leads-to-get-5-contracts-in-1-week.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Having a Say in Your Fate as an Agent</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/f-rucmXaEuY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s focus is on something that has the real estate industry buzzing with conversation lately: What’s happening with disruptive companies like Opendoor and Redfin? More importantly, what fate is destined for the real estate agent amid all of this? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s explore this a little today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics that interest you most: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:50—A brief explanation of the insights I gained by attending Inman’s “Disconnect” event&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:40—Who the players are and what the market looks like &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:15—The piece of the market that each major “player” is projected to capture&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:00—Which players make up the largest base in the middle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:44—Zillow’s approach to deciding where the best leads go: solo agents, teams, or brokerages &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:35—What does all of this mean for you? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:05—Given the current and future landscape, how can you position yourself ahead of this opportunity? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you found this conversation helpful. If you have any questions in regard to today’s topic or anything else, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. Until next time, remember: Don’t just be an agent. Be the expert.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 12:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/having-a-say-in-your-fate-as-an-agent.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/having-a-say-in-your-fate-as-an-agent.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Success Interview: Kelly Baldwin</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p8-2Rjm9QRw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Episode No. 3 of our “Agent Success” series! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I have the great privilege of sitting down with and shining the spotlight on Kelly Baldwin. The story of our meeting began when she happened to be renting a vacation property that I own in Lake Tahoe. As a result, we forged a friendship and she decided to break into real estate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just five months into full production, she’s already closed 13 transactions to the tune of $15 million in business and is on pace to close an amazing 30 transactions by the end of 2019.      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in our interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:58—What was Kelly doing before getting into real estate and what led her to pursue this new path? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:30—What was her first position with the team? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:12—How many real estate-related conversations did Kelly have versus the number of people she called in her first month? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:08—What ultimately inspired Kelly to join our team? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:22—How much was uncertainty a factor for Kelly in the beginning? How did she persevere in spite of those feelings? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9:37—Where does she foresee her career in real estate headed? What life goals have been made possible thanks to this new direction? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11:45—How has Kelly’s experience been in the culture we’ve worked to foster? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:45—In closing, what can Kelly most attribute to her success and personal growth? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for tuning in for this segment in our “Agent Success” series, and I appreciate Kelly taking some time to share her experience working with our team so far! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like more information on how you can double your business year over year and you’re trying to get to the next level, go ahead and surf through our blog. Also, register for our monthly mastermind group to receive our monthly updates and training video on our success-driven tactics and strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 13:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/success-interview-kelly-baldwin.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/success-interview-kelly-baldwin.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Go From Agent to CEO of Your Real Estate Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WrkGyr-QSuE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can you move from being a real estate agent to becoming the CEO of your own business? &lt;strong&gt;I’ve done it myself, and I’d like to show you how you can do it too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey took about three years, and I’ve grown from $3 million in production to over $165 million. My mentor, who made 300 sales each year compared to my 15, told me that the problems start with EID: entrepreneurial idiot disease. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;80% of real estate is 20$ to 25$ per hour work.&lt;/strong&gt; If you relegate yourself to doing these low-cost tasks, you only have 20% of your time that you can spend doing the $200-per-hour work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to figure out what your time is worth by creating your income goals. Let’s say you want to make $500,000 a year. 40 hours per week for 50 weeks is 2,000 hours. Divide $500,000 by 2,000 and you get an amount of $250 an hour. Therefore, anything that’s not worth $250 an hour should be off your plate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you relegate yourself to doing these low-cost tasks, you only have 20% of your time that you can spend doing the $200-per-hour work.%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-go-from-agent-to-ceo-of-your-real-estate-business.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you relegate yourself to doing these low-cost tasks, you only have 20% of your time that you can spend doing the $200-per-hour work.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next, we introduce leverage by getting other people to work for you.&lt;/strong&gt; To effectively grow your business, you need a great administrative staff to coordinate transactions. You want a full-time admin once you hit 15 to 20 transactions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After this, you need predictable, scalable lead generation.&lt;/strong&gt; Most agents only utilize open houses and spheres of influence, but you need to create farms and use the internet to find leads. If you have an admin team and lead generation techniques in place, you’ll be ready to add agents to your business and become a CEO. And since you’re driving business to these agents, they’ll stay loyal to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 13:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-go-from-agent-to-ceo-of-your-real-estate-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-go-from-agent-to-ceo-of-your-real-estate-business.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Nneka Sold $26 Million in Real Estate in 9 Months</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qEUI64iYOE8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both before and after joining the Real Estate Experts, Nneka Jenkins has had quite the journey in real estate. Today I sat down with her to talk about her story of success and what she has achieved since joining our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the interview.&lt;/strong&gt; Feel free to watch the full video or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;0:50—Her journey prior to joining the Real Estate Experts&lt;br /&gt;5:00—On joining the Real Estate Experts: Adjusting to a new environment and new practices&lt;br /&gt;9:20—What were Nneka’s business practices like before joining the team? After?&lt;br /&gt;12:10—Nneka’s first year as an agent was hugely successful. How much has she accomplished in the first quarter of 2019 so far?&lt;br /&gt;12:50—Nneka’s advice for agents who are looking to do more business; mastering your sphere of influence&lt;br /&gt;15:45—Nneka’s outlook on the future in terms of her career and her lifestyle&lt;br /&gt;17:40—Closing remarks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so thankful for Nneka taking the time to share the intimate details of her journey with me. We’re thrilled to work with her, and I’m excited to see the next chapter of her business as it progresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about improving your career in real estate or joining the Real Estate Experts team, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you. And remember: Don’t just be an agent—be an expert.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 12:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-nneka-sold-26-million-in-real-estate-in-9-months.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-nneka-sold-26-million-in-real-estate-in-9-months.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winning in a Multiple-Offer Situation</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hrCcBO5t8bM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are seven strategies you can use to help your buyers win out in a multiple-offer situation: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Know the market.&lt;/strong&gt; By this I mean you need to study the recent comparable sales and, more importantly, the most recent pending sales. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Go big or go homeless.&lt;/strong&gt; Obviously, you want to make an offer that’s higher than the last known comparable pending sale. If there were four offers on a recent pending sale, that means three buyers who lost out on the home will be looking to offer a higher price the next time around. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Consider using an escalation clause.&lt;/strong&gt; This is an addendum to your client’s purchase agreement that guarantees they’ll offer a higher price than the next highest offer up to a certain amount. Talk to the listing agent before you use this clause, though, because some agents have never seen it before and might not understand how it works. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=In a quick market like ours, the first person to the party is often the winner.%20http://localhost:4000/winning-in-a-multiple-offer-situation.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“In a quick market like ours, the first person to the party is often the winner.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Waive as many contingencies as possible.&lt;/strong&gt; Get your buyer pre-approved before they make an offer so that they aren’t carrying any loan or appraisal contingencies with them. Many sellers in the Bay Area also do pre-inspections, so if you and your client are comfortable trusting a pre-inspection, you can waive your own inspection contingency. If the seller hasn’t done a pre-inspection, you can still get the inspection contingency waived by asking the listing agent to have it done prior to making your offer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Put down a huge earnest money deposit.&lt;/strong&gt; A customary earnest money deposit in our area is 3% of the purchase price. If your buyer has the funds, have them put down 10%. Your client’s not taking on any more risk, because the liquidated damages clause maximizes liquidated damages at 3%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Write a love letter to the seller.&lt;/strong&gt; Writing a love letter has helped our team’s clients win out in a multiple-offer situation even when they didn’t offer the highest price. Have your client include pictures of their own family, and if possible, have them shoot a quick video on their phone that you can then text or email the listing agent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Create urgency.&lt;/strong&gt; In a quick market like ours, the first person to the party is often the winner. With that in mind, consider sending a pre-emptive offer to the listing agent. They have an obligation to show the seller that offer, so you don’t need to ask permission. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any more questions about how to come out on top in a multiple-offer situation, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 12:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/winning-in-a-multiple-offer-situation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/winning-in-a-multiple-offer-situation.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Success Spotlight - Tony Fery:  How to Go From 0 to 36 Deals a Year</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fMZSveqnky8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Episode 2 of our “Agent Success” series! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this series, I hold interviews with some of our team’s up-and-coming stars in the sphere of real estate and pick their brain about their journey—where they come from, their challenges along the way, and where they’re headed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without further ado, I’m super excited to introduce today’s guest: Tony Fery. Our friendship actually predates his emergence in real estate, and as someone fairly new to the industry, he’s already on pace to do 36 transactions this year alone. He’s certainly proven to be an asset to our team.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in our interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:40—Where was Tony before cracking into real estate? What caused him to take the leap?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:07—What was Tony’s transition into real estate like? How did it help him once he launched?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:02—What kind of success did Tony have in those first six months?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:05—When he faced some obstacles in his business, what allowed him to persevere? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:01—How did Tony use the “Future Self” tool to identify who he wanted to be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14:53—What business does Tony currently have in the pipeline? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16:40—With all of Tony’s commitments, how is his mindset now different from when he started? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22:10—What possibilities and aspirations does Tony foresee for his future in real estate? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;23:12—What final words can Tony offer to others? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for tuning in for this segment in our “Agent Success” series! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like more information on how you can double your business year over year and you’re trying to go to the next level, please &lt;a href=&quot;https://bearealexpert.com/strategy-call/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;grab a time slot on the calendar here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to schedule a 30-minute strategy session. Or you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdupJkt2cjDwMzfiFaH0Sl7SdLa_cPfnolaCEiGE5O6_84HSA/viewform&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;register for our Monthly Mastermind&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to our team. We look forward to hearing from you! Remember: Don’t just be an agent—be the expert.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 09:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/success-spotlight-tony-fery-how-to-go-from-0-to-36-deals-a-year.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/success-spotlight-tony-fery-how-to-go-from-0-to-36-deals-a-year.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Compass, Zillow, Redfin &amp;  The Fate of Agents</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/1oCzX5GRab8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real estate landscape is changing. I’ve gotten phone calls from a number of agents recently with questions about what’s going on, so I thought I’d explore the matter with all of you today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;00:28 - An introduction to today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;02:39 - How digital platforms are changing the future of our industry&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;06:10 - How various digital platforms operate in different price ranges of our market&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:34 - How technology-driven models will impact real estate professionals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11:35 - Why Zillow dominates the median price ranges in our market, and how one other major player (Homelight) operates in those ranges &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16:35 - What agents must understand about leveraging the companies mentioned today&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17:11 - Why there may be fewer real estate agents in the future&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17:56 - How to decide what range(s) you want to do business in &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:55 - A conclusion to today’s message&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/compass-zillow-redfin-the-fate-of-agents.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/compass-zillow-redfin-the-fate-of-agents.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
