<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Silicon Valley Real Estate Podcast with Brett Jennings</title>
    <link>localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Brett Jennings Real Estate Experts - your professional Silicon Valley Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Brett Jennings</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-04-16 13:48:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Brett Jennings</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Silicon Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Brett@TheRealExperts.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Brett Jennings</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Brett Jennings</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Silicon Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Silicon Valley Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Brett Jennings Real Estate Experts - your professional Silicon Valley Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Journey From Agent to CEO: How to Grow From 10 -130 Deals per Year</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/the-journey-from-agent-to-ceo-how-to-grow-from-10-130-deals-per-year.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <author>Brett Jennings</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-16 13:07:45 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+The+Journey+From+Agent+to+CEO-+How+to+Grow+From+10+-130+Deals+per+Year.mp4</guid>
        <description>

How can you move from being a real estate agent to becoming the CEO of your own business? I’ve done it myself, and I’d like to show you how you can do it too.

The journey took about three years, and I’ve grown from $3 million in production to over $165 million. My mentor, who made 300 sales each year compared to my 15, told me that the problems start with EID: entrepreneurial idiot disease. 

80% of real estate is 20$ to 25$ per hour work. If you relegate yourself to doing these low-cost tasks, you only have 20% of your time that you can spend doing the $200-per-hour work.

You need to figure out what your time is worth by creating your income goals. Let’s say you want to make $500,000 a year. 40 hours per week for 50 weeks is 2,000 hours. Divide $500,000 by 2,000 and you get an amount of $250 an hour. Therefore, anything that’s not worth $250 an hour should be off your plate.

“If you relegate yourself to doing these low-cost tasks, you only have 20% of your time that you can spend doing the $200-per-hour work.”

Next, we introduce leverage by getting other people to work for you. To effectively grow your business, you need a great administrative staff to coordinate transactions. You want a full-time admin once you hit 15 to 20 transactions. 

After this, you need predictable, scalable lead generation. Most agents only utilize open houses and spheres of influence, but you need to create farms and use the internet to find leads. If you have an admin team and lead generation techniques in place, you’ll be ready to add agents to your business and become a CEO. And since you’re driving business to these agents, they’ll stay loyal to you.

If you have any other questions, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+The+Journey+From+Agent+to+CEO-+How+to+Grow+From+10+-130+Deals+per+Year.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+The+Journey+From+Agent+to+CEO-+How+to+Grow+From+10+-130+Deals+per+Year.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I became the CEO of my own real estate business in three years. You can do it too, and here’s how.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Brett Jennings</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I became the CEO of my own real estate business in three years. You can do it too, and here’s how.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Silicon Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Success Spotllight - Tony Fery:  How to Go From 0 to 36 Deals a Year</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/success-spotllight-tony-fery-how-to-go-from-0-to-36-deals-a-year.html</link>
        
          <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        <author>Brett Jennings</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-08 09:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+Success+Spotllight+-+Tony+Fery-+How+to+Go+From+0+to+36+Deals+a+Year.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Welcome to Episode 2 of our “Agent Success” series! 

In this series, I hold interviews with some of our team’s up-and-coming stars in the sphere of real estate and pick their brain about their journey—where they come from, their challenges along the way, and where they’re headed.

Without further ado, I’m super excited to introduce today’s guest: Tony Fery. Our friendship actually predates his emergence in real estate, and as someone fairly new to the industry, he’s already on pace to do 36 transactions this year alone. He’s certainly proven to be an asset to our team.  

Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in our interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: 

1:40—Where was Tony before cracking into real estate? What caused him to take the leap?

6:07—What was Tony’s transition into real estate like? How did it help him once he launched?  

8:02—What kind of success did Tony have in those first six months?

10:05—When he faced some obstacles in his business, what allowed him to persevere? 

13:01—How did Tony use the “Future Self” tool to identify who he wanted to be?

14:53—What business does Tony currently have in the pipeline? 

16:40—With all of Tony’s commitments, how is his mindset now different from when he started? 

22:10—What possibilities and aspirations does Tony foresee for his future in real estate? 

23:12—What final words can Tony offer to others? 

Thanks for tuning in for this segment in our “Agent Success” series! 

If you’d like more information on how you can double your business year over year and you’re trying to go to the next level, please grab a time slot on the calendar here to schedule a 30-minute strategy session. Or you can register for our Monthly Mastermind here! Lastly, click here for our double-your-business webinar where we open our own business playbook for you! 

If you have any other questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to our team. We look forward to hearing from you! Remember: Don’t just be an agent—be the expert.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+Success+Spotllight+-+Tony+Fery-+How+to+Go+From+0+to+36+Deals+a+Year.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+Success+Spotllight+-+Tony+Fery-+How+to+Go+From+0+to+36+Deals+a+Year.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Hear how Tony Fery came into the Real Estate Experts model and doubled his business every year.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Brett Jennings</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Hear how Tony Fery came into the Real Estate Experts model and doubled his business every year.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Silicon Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Compass, Zillow, Redfin &  The Fate of Agents</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/compass-zillow-redfin-the-fate-of-agents.html</link>
        
          <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Brett Jennings</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-01 12:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+Compass%2C+Zillow%2C+Redfin+%26+The+Fate+of+Agents.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The real estate landscape is changing. I’ve gotten phone calls from a number of agents recently with questions about what’s going on, so I thought I’d explore the matter with all of you today. 

Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: 

00:28 - An introduction to today’s topic

02:39 - How digital platforms are changing the future of our industry

06:10 - How various digital platforms operate in different price ranges of our market

10:34 - How technology-driven models will impact real estate professionals

11:35 - Why Zillow dominates the median price ranges in our market, and how one other major player (Homelight) operates in those ranges 

16:35 - What agents must understand about leveraging the companies mentioned today

17:11 - Why there may be fewer real estate agents in the future

17:56 - How to decide what range(s) you want to do business in 

18:55 - A conclusion to today’s message

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+Compass%2C+Zillow%2C+Redfin+%26+The+Fate+of+Agents.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Brett+Jennings/+Videos/2019/April/Real+Estate+Experts-+Compass%2C+Zillow%2C+Redfin+%26+The+Fate+of+Agents.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our industry is changing, so, with this message, I’d like to highlight a few things agents can expect to see moving forward.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Brett Jennings</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our industry is changing, so, with this message, I’d like to highlight a few things agents can expect to see moving forward.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Silicon Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Brett Jennings</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Brett Jennings</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Brett Jennings Real Estate Experts - your professional Silicon Valley Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
